[ED.
Emitune Main ending
It's morning time, and it's time for me to go to Ebi City Junior High School.
I'm the one who's going to be the star of the show, aren't I?
I'm Sakuraeiko Kanade I'm Sarate I'm the thread of the plate, and I feel like I can work if I have it, I'm Naganishi, please.
I don't know, this show is a show race without the influence of Downtown Matsumoto as a judge for the Meta Battle.
Booburushi.
This week, we have the second part of the battle of the 500th anniversary of Ebichu Minamiya Nen.
Last week, we had Coconan Sakurai, Hoshina Mirai, Ayaka Yasumoto's Ito-san team, Noka Kazamino, and Ema Sakurai's Nassan team performing their material.
Buvershi
If you say that the story made by Mr. Ito is 47 seconds long, it will have a strong impact on the audience.
I'm so relieved... I'm so relieved... I don't have anything to do.
I don't have anything to do.
Booby dooby dooby dooby dooby dooby dooby doo.
Boo-bah-shh.
So here's a song for you to listen to, and the song is "Yumen," and it's a joint collaboration with a private shrimp master.
Yumen, the shrimp chew. We want to hear from you on the show.
The email address is,
Ebi,
Atmark,
MBS,
1179.com.
Well, the EbiChu members are preparing their stories for this week, so it's just the two of us.
I've seen the story, I've seen the story, I've seen the story, I've seen the story, I've seen the story, I've seen the story, I've seen the story, I've seen the story, I've seen the story, I've checked it out naturally, I've seen it, how did it go?
I don't have any more... and I keep remembering it.
It's so weird... it's so weird... even though I made it myself, it's already a good memory.
Harunaka-sanWell, the two of us were practicing so much that we were buying juice at the vending machine while the two of us were buying it.
I felt a little sorry for them, because they really looked like young comedians, you know, before the show, like the sleeves of M-1.
Let's get started.
Are you ready to begin?
It's really rare to see the two of them looking so nervous.
The first team of the second half will be the Tanaka team, and we're Yamanashi Hananaka and Yamanashi Yamashiko.
okay, okay... be prepared... be calm and relaxed... as usual... it's very important...
Okay, first of all, I'd like to start with the duo of Mae-Arika and Yamanashi Yamashiko.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm Rika Nakayama.
I'm Riko Nakayama.
I'm Rikako Nakayama.
Nakayama Yama, Rikako.
Oh, Rika, your birthday is coming soon.
It's in December. It's not soon at all.
Well, well, I understand why you're afraid of your birthday.
What do you mean?
You're not that old yet.
Oh, so, I've already bought Rika's birthday present this year.
Oh, no. It's still half a year away.
I'm sure she'll be happy.
Well, I'm glad you've been thinking about it that long.
What did you buy her, by the way?
I won't tell you that. I'll tell you on the day of my birthday.
I wonder what it is. Give me a hint.
Is it something to hang in your room? Or is it something you wear?
Wear it? I wouldn't wear it. You're an idiot.
I don't know what it is. It's not something you wear.
If I saw someone wearing it, I'd say, "Did your parents hit you, my best friend bear?
I don't know, I don't know. I don't even know why I'm suddenly speaking in Kansai dialect.
Oh, something to decorate.
Then I guess it's something to be decorated. Decorative things.
Well, it's something to eat. What? Food for decoration?
Do they have an expiration date? Don't worry, it's fine. If you work hard, it will last for about 20 years.
Twenty years? And you can decorate it? What? Like a string?
How is that possible? No one decorates with string! I don't care what you do, either way!
Is that what they say? No, but you're right. Sorry, sorry.
Because they say it lasts 20 years. It's more like a living organism.
A living thing? That's a lie. I'm sorry. I really don't know.
Big hint. Tell me the first letter.
It starts with "a" and ends with "na".
Aloana.
Hey, is it Aloana? You're not Aloana, are you? Tell me it's not Aloana!
I can't tell you what it is yet!
No one gives a creature on its birthday!
Oh, you said something about giving birth to an Aloana, didn't you?
Well, we'll see what it is on your birthday!
I'm afraid my birthday is coming...
Oh, by the way, Rika-chan, do you have a space this big at home?
It's Aroana, right? You mean the space for Aroana's hydrogen clothes, right?
No! I was just curious!
I mean, can you eat aloana?
Oh, by the way, Rika-chan, are you okay with crickets?
They are aloana, right? You mean aloana food, right?
No! I'm just wondering who is okay with bugs and such!
I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't! Absolutely not!
And aloanas live for 20 years?
I heard they can grow to be about a meter long.
Hey, I'm in trouble! Even if I got an aloana, I'm not sure I could grow it!
Can you please reconsider?
You didn't say your birthday present was an aloana!
What? What starts with a and ends with na?
A big African flower.Big flowers in Africa
Oh!
What? You can eat it?
I mean, can you eat them?
Oh, my God!
Thank you very much!
That's great!
You've got it memorized!
Amazing!
I watched you in practice, but your performance was the best! Perfect!
No, you were magnificent!
Excellent!
Your pauses were perfect!
First and foremost, how can you do such a serious talk!
It's a real talking problem!
This is the kind of stuff you could have done on Oswald!
The last one, "kowa"... I use that a lot.
I was aware of that! Mr. Ito!
That's amazing!
It had an Oswald feel to it!
Perfect!
You didn't even chew the personnel!
Perfect timing! Rikchan's weird Kansai dialect was perfect!
Kazuyama's surprise was perfect!
Let's hear your impressions first! How did you like it, Mr. Kazuyama?
Yes, it was great! I didn't succeed even once in practice!
I'm glad I was able to do it on the day!
I was so nervous!
We had a few chances to play together, but the real performance was the best!
Ricchan usually uses Kansai dialect in the corners and so on!
I was a little conscious of that!
I never thought I'd see the day when I could make use of it!
What a corner!
That was amazing!
You slept for about 3 minutes!
You did it right!
Comedy is playing the part of a comedian! Who hasn't done that before!
They are two guys from Tokyo Progressive University!
The conversation was really natural and easy to listen to!
It was easy to listen to!
If it's in the middle of the show, it's in the middle of the radio show, but it's such a blowout!
No, no, no, no, no!
Surely! Surely!
What did you guys do wrong?
No problem! I wasn't aware of that!
At least give me an example of how much!
That's the point, Mr. Toshinobu!
It didn't resonate with me at all!
It was perfect!
I'm screwed!
Let's move on!
That was brilliant!
Rika-chan turned her head forward at some points while she was speaking!
I liked the way she was aware of the audience!
That's a lot of fun!
When I get nervous! I would turn my head to the side!
You're right, we do talk alone!
It's good to see your usual style! The way you talk!
There was no lie!
No lie!
There is no lie between them!
They are great!
Well, thank you very much for the working team!
It was a good project!
Good stuff!
So, next up is Nakanishi's team
Let's go to the Nakanishi team's trio of Kobayashi Kaho, Nakamura Ona, and Fukuho Inono!
Are all three of you ready?
OK?
OK!
Okay.
Now then, for the second half, Kaho Kobayashi, Ino Ino, Sky Ino-chan, let's have your trio story, please.
Yes, I'm Kobayashi, I've transferred to this class today. Nice to meet you.
Yes, well, Mr. Kobayashi's seat is in the front row, next to Mikio Soneame.
Yes, please take care of him.
Okay, I'm going.
I will take your attendance. Answer in a loud voice.
Masao Abe, captain of the volleyball team
Pleased to meet you.
President of the Student Council Hikaru Inoue
There's a president? Amazing.
Baseball Club Ace Takashi Inoue
Akira Ito, head of the Shogi Club
Class president Masahiko Uno
Swimming club captain Kyoko Eto
Kendo club vice-captain Yoshie Enami
Basketball team substitute Makoto Ehara
Miyoko Ohno, manager of the soccer club
Do you say this every time? Why not just say their names?
Koichi Otani, substitute field hockey player
Doesn't it take a lot of time? This.Doesn't it take a lot of time? It is.
Shigeo Kato, Bicycle commuter
Don't you have to say that? There are others, aren't there?
People who don't like me
That's a no-no.
Kohji Kanegawa
You don't have to reply either.
Lacrosse Club Captain Kaneko Kaneko
I'm curious about the kanji. Can you write Kaneko, Kaneko?
Karate Club Member Inuo Kinoshita
Inudo.
Hitter club member, Kihara, Sarujiro.
Sarujiro.
Table tennis club member... Kubota, Kiji, Matsu.
Dog, Monkey, Kiji.
Then, that's next.
Kintaro Kondo, member of the track and field club.
No way, Kintaro.
I was expecting Peach.
Handicraft club member Kintaro Momoyama Momotaro
Peaches? No, Kintaro, peaches.
Shoplifting team Yu Sasaki
Snatch-and-run team, Ken Sheayama
Katsuragi pick-up squad Daiki Shimizu
Bicycle thief Masako Segawa
Theft unit, Akira Sudo
Work Yaba
Crime fantasista
Crime fantasista?
SONEYAMA Mikiyo
It's the person next door. Next to the person who looks the most dangerous by night.
Double surname
Double surname?
Matsumoto, Hayashi
Double last name. Kiiiio
Funniest big slash number one
the man who never slips
The man who never, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever slip
Please stop him!
very funny at first sight!
Omoshiro! Name is funny!
Taro Nakagawa
A guy with nothing.
Nothing unique, but looks rather unique.
Kazuo Nakatani, Taro Nakagawa's general strike
Taro Nakagawa's bodyguard Shunsuke Nishio
Aiko Nishida as Taro Nakagawa's escort
Noriko Nishimura as Taro Nakagawa's morning passerby
No, the Fukuri composition of impersonality is amazing
The impersonality is getting happiness
Ecko is a pitfall of love Mako Momotaka
Yes?
What? You're kidding, right?
She looks just like Ino Kunimoya from Ebichu?
That's all of you present.
Sir, I wasn't invited.
Oh, I forgot.
Always smiling, Kaho Kobayashi, the toy box.
No, that's not it.
Thank you very much.
This is wonderful.
You were the best at the booth.
It's nice.
It's a little gory.
Koyoha Hanaho is going to be the lucky one.
I hadn't thought of that.
She's a talkative transfer student.
He was a talkative transfer student.
Popular.
You picked up everything.
You picked it all up.
Wait a minute.
I like your system.
It's good, but...
I'm nervous. Nervous.
I think you've said before that Yuno-chan isn't good at Nakanishi.
Are you not good at Yuno-chan too, Nakanishi?
Well, I dared to ask Yuno-chan just one word.
There weren't too many, but...
What did you think of Yuno-chan when you got the script?
Oh, it's easy to remember.
Easy to remember
Easy to remember doesn't mean anything.
I didn't want it to be understood.
That's the essence of it.
Yuno-chan, first of all, it's only yes, right?
That's right.
Yunosky, in the first place...
You write.
She does it while reading a list.
Koha Hanaho remembers this.You must be Koha Kaho who remembers this story.
I was really, really nervous last night and couldn't sleep.
Amazing.
But you did it without dropping it all.
You did it without spilling anything.
You even made a good face.
Every time, every time you look forward.
You just keep plugging away.
I'm glad you did that.
I hope she was okay.
I liked that you were a little different from the usual Koyoha Kaho.
I've never seen her like that before.
You're right.
He's so quick and clear.
That's for sure.
I've never seen him like that before.
I'm pretty sure he's not a quick commentator.
Normally.
You're not a comedian, are you?
But if you look closely... there's nothing but goofs on this team.
That's why I was a little worried.
Someone has to do it.
But it's hard to read the roster.
It's amazing... you can read the names without chewing any of them.
It's not so bad.
If the teacher bites it, he'll run away, laughing.
It's a waste of time.
And you did it so well.
It's the most difficult position.
It was difficult, wasn't it?
So there was a part in the middle where I had to say the part of the instrument with nothing attached to the head, or the part with nothing attached to the head.
But when I asked him to pause for the part with just the name, he did it perfectly.
It's a great story.
It's all about taste, isn't it?
Sense of style.
Yes.
Yuno's sense again.
Yes, actually, people around her think she's the one.
Yes, it's important.
It's nerve-wracking to say it so late in the game.
That's right.
How many points did you get for your yes?
Well, how many points?
I wonder what it was.
I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. 100?
I don't know, I don't know. No, it was a perfect 100.
But you did a great job while we were waiting for the show.
You were doing a great job. I was really drawn in.
Yes, I don't know if you're listening to the radio, but she was acting the whole time.
I was really excited to see what she would come up with.
That was wonderful!
Yay! That's great, everyone!
How did you remember it? I was so nervous!
So, thank you very much to everyone at Kiyomi Nakanishi.
Thank you very much. - That was wonderful.
That was great!
Now, after this, we will announce the results of the competition and see which team had the most fun!
Enjoy!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Coconutta everyone!
Let's Party Night
Kashikomi kashikomi moshikomi
Let's Party Night!
Now that we've finished the stories from all four countries, I'll tell you which team was the funniest, the two of you five.
I think it's about 5 people.
M1 something, right?
M17, right?
You used to have five, and King Cobb Court had five.
Oh, I see.
That's how a jury works.
Judges are women.
Momomomo.
Firs, too.
How confident are you? Of your team?
What do you think, gentlemen?
What?
What do you think?
Yes! Oh!
Do you have it? Yes?
I like it. I think it's number one.
Yes. Yes.
That's good. I have one, too.
Elsewhere in Cat's Eye. I thought it was at a disadvantage because it was last week.
I thought I was the most interesting of the four.
I see. Excellent. I'm in.
Me, me, me, me, me. My cat's eye.
I'm thinking that Mr. Ito's cat's eye might be my cat's eye.
I see.
So you thought you could win with two pairs today.
Win or lose, you're all so frustrated.Whether you win or lose, you'll all be frustrated.
I would like to announce the same results.
Now that we have received the tally, let's start with the third place or something.
First of all, third place or something.
We're in third place out of four teams.
I'm so nervous.
I wish the fans had been called.
Okay, here it is.
The third place winner of the Ibishunai Yanen story battle is...
Yes, I'm getting nervous.
We got one vote!
Nakanishi Team
Oh!
Surprisingly...
Third place!
Third place is not even delicious!
That's for sure.
Third place.
Maybe not the best.
One vote?
What the hell?
After all that hard work.
I put it in for the third-place team.
The person who cast this vote...
It was you.
I'm very happy... even if we came in third.
That's right.
I'll treasure this vote.
I'll live to see tomorrow.
Make every vote count.
I'll live on from tomorrow.
I will do my best.
How are you doing, Ino-chan?
I'm glad I got to say yes.
First of all...
I'm glad.
How's Sky?
I'm glad you stopped shouting.
You look refreshed.
How's Ms. Nakanishi?
It's wonderful.
You just said "one vote".
I...
My wife.
And my two sons.
That adds up to four votes.
That makes five votes for you.
The winner.
Congratulations.
I don't know what's going on.
So, third place went to the Nakanishi team.
Thank you very much!
Next, I would like to announce the second place!
Two teams tied!
What?
What do you mean "tied"?
You mean we're tied for first place?
More like a tie for first place.
We're in a tie for second place.
We just came in second.
There was a tie for first place between two teams.
The Midwest team came in second.
So that's how it is.
And there's...
There's one big pitfall.
Ito, I just realized...
Third place
Second place got one vote.
First place was second place.
They tied for first place with two votes each.
The staff who chose the B team's story
The staff member who chose team B's story...
They said they'd copy and paste it.
There are no more votes.
You're not in.
Either way, it's impossible.
That's for sure.
Why didn't anyone notice the rule?
It's not here.
This is... unexpected.
I'm getting nervous.
We'll figure out B team's punishment later.
Let's do that.
I'd like to announce the two teams tied for first place.
Yes, please.
Let's see...
Shrimp in the middle, take a joke.
The two teams tied for first place are...
Let's go!
Let's go!Buber paper
That's what I'm talking about, Rittern and before, apparently.
Chairman's Day.
Congratulations!
I'm sure you're right... that was the best speech I've had all day... and if I don't win, well...
I'll go to Starbucks and practice before the show.
Boo-hoo!
I was afraid I wouldn't get it, but I'm glad I did.
It's a confidence booster.
Boober.
Booby!
Booby.
how have you been doing this summer since the Ibis bloodbath?
I'm not fresh, but I'm still able to win the first place...
Boo boo!
I'm okay with that, but I can't wait to report to Aya and Mire-chan.
I can't wait to report to Aya and Mire-chan.
I thought you guys were drinking.
Master's forehead now.
Oshiwado is at the bottom of the list.
So first and second place goes to Oswald, and third and fourth to Nasaka.
That's how it is.
This is still, you know, that 47 seconds in improvement.
So, when thinking about which to cut.
So, I was beaten by the length of time.
I see. It can't be helped.
Now that this last place has been confirmed, let's go to the penalty game.
Yes.
Let's think about it.
So, that's all for now.
And now, I would like to announce a new project.
Ebichu Nanyanen will be collaborating with Kuji Live, a media specialized in online lottery.
Online lottery.
Kuji-live is a media where you can enjoy raffle draws for limited-edition goods without any losers.
This time, as a special project of EBICHU Nanyanen linked Kuji Live, we will deliver limited contents such as videos and voices that can be obtained only at Kuji Live.
Now, let us announce the contents to be won in the lottery live.
The fifth prize is a picture, and each EBICHU member will get one picture of what they think is their best moment.
And the winner will get a limited-edition picture of EBINAKA NANYANEN by EBINAKA NAKANISHI.
Wow.
I wonder if it's okay to say that I'm going to do this.
You all got this, right?
And the 4th and 3rd prizes are voices, from Ebichu Nan-Yanen's famous corner jingle song audition,
You can win a 10-second jingle recorded by all the members of EBINAKA Nan-Yanen Kuji Live only.
The 4th prize is Nasunakanishi's jingle song.
The 3rd prize will be the jingle song of EBICHU members.
I'm getting in here and there.
I'm sorry.
And the 2nd prize is a video of Cocona Sakurai's favorite points of the EBICHU members, which I, Cocona Sakurai, shot with my own smartphone.
This is courtesy of Kuji Live.
The percentage of 2nd prize is higher than other events.
Please complete all kinds.
And the 1st prize is also a movie,
It will be a video of more than 30 seconds in which two members of Ebichu express their appreciation to the winners.
The winner will be able to choose from 5 pairs of 2 Ebichu members and their names will be read out.
The event will run from June 15 to 30, 2012 and will cost 330 yen a piece.
Thank you very much.
So, I would like to go on to the ending of the event.
This week's closing song is an update of myself as a private shrimp shicu.
Here is an announcement.
The Spring Tour Private Ebishitu Role and Spring Tour 2023 100% Ebitsum is currently underway.
The tour is going to 17 parks in 14 cities across the country.
My outside line live Ibaraki park has sold out.
Thank you very much.
There are still tickets available for Sendai Park, so please come.
Also this year, EBITCHU Summer Family Performance, or Famien in Yamanakako 2023, will be held again.
The event will be held at Yamanakako Koryu Plaza Kirara and Theater Hibiki on Saturday, August 5 and Sunday, August 6, 2023.
Please check the official website for details.
In addition, the 14th single, "How are you doing today? is now on sale.
The siblings' song, "How are you doing today? is a cute song with lyrics written by Sho Yamamoto.
The music video is now on view and features many cute expressions of the members, so please listen to it.
Also, we are currently conducting a test of "How are you doing today? s "Nukei Hear Music Test" is now being conducted.
Please check the special site for details.
What's going on?
It was the sound of Kokuboi, Yuna Nakamura, the human sound of Ozol, the working sound of Ozol, Nasunakashi Nasuto, and Nakanishi.
See you next week. Bye bye.
After this, I resumed this game.
I resumed this game.
I resumed this game
I resumed this gameI have resumed this game.
I resumed this game.
I resumed this game